This course will have five lessons.
本课程分为五课
In this first lesson, we'll be giving you an overview of what A/B testing is
第一课中 我们会大概介绍什么是 A/B 测试
and what it can and can't be used for.
以及测试可用和不可用的情况
We'll also go over an example A/B test from start to finish so
我们将一起从头到尾地了解 A/B 测试的示例
that you can see what the whole process looks like.
以便于你可以看到整个过程是怎样的
In that example, we'll first choose a metric for an experiment,
在示例中 我们首先要选择用于试验的一项指标
then review some necessary statistics, then we'll design our experiment, and
查看必要的统计结果 随后我们将设计我们自己的试验
finally, we'll analyze the results.
最终 我们将分析结果
Then each subsequent lesson of the course will dive into more detail
在之后的课程中 我们将深入了解
on a particular part of the process.
整个过程中某个部分的具体细节
In lesson two, you'll will be learning about how to protect
在第二课中 你将学到如何保护
the participants of your experiment, and what questions you should be
试验中的参与者 以及你应该不断问自己
asking yourself regarding the ethicality of experiments.
哪些关于实验伦理性方面的问题
In lesson three, we'll go into more detail on choosing and
在第三课中 我们将更具体地探讨如何选择
characterizing metrics to use when evaluating your experiment.
和定义用于实验评估的指标
In lesson four, we'll talk more about designing your experiment, which
在第四课中 我们将更多的讨论如何设计试验
includes choosing which users go in your control group and your experiment group.
包括选择哪些用户进入对照组 哪些用户进入到实验组
And, in lesson five, we'll go over lots of examples of what your results could
在第五课中 我们将查看大量示例 说明你的结果
look like, how to analyze those results, and how to draw valid conclusions.
可能出现的形式 如何分析上述结果 如何得出有效的结论
Now, you won't need any prior experience with A/B testing in order to take
现在 要参加这个课程 你不需要任何以前使用 A/B 测试的经验
this course, because we'll be covering it from the ground up.
因为我们将从最基础的部分开始
And you won't need any programming experience either,
同时你也不需要任何编程经验
because this course won't cover how to implement an A/B testing framework.
因为本课程不会包含如何执行 A/B 测试的框架
It's about how to design and analyze experiments.
本课程讲的是如何设计和分析实验
Introductory knowledge of statistics, on the other hand, will be required.
另一方面 我们需要的是统计学入门知识
So if you need to brush up, check out the links in the instructors notes.
因此 如果你需要复习 就查看讲师注释中的链接
Now throughout the course, I'll be going over lots of examples and
在整个课程中 我将向大家展示大量示例
giving you opportunities to practice what you're learning.
你也拥有运用所学内容的机会
I'll also be having conversations with Dianne and
我还会与 Dianne 和 Carrier
Carrie about their experiences in A/B testing.
一起讨论她们在 A/B 测试中的经验
Let's do that now.
我们现在开始